Organisations

IU Finance Club, *Member of Academic Department* 09/2021 – present

Main responsibility:

- Analyze data and build content for Equity Research Program, Market Research Program, and News Program.
- Enter into organizing club public events such as FINSPEED, etc.

PROGRAMS OF IUF

- Equity Research Performance: Vinamilk, An Phat Bioplastics
- Market Research Performance: Agriculture Industry
- News Performance: Find and sum up financial hot news

Achievement: Research, Summary, and Data analysis

FINSPEED CONTEST

FINSPEED is a financial competition organized by IUF of International University. It gives students the opportunity to gain experience in analyzing corporate financial statements and equity research.

Main responsibility:

- Find contact points of (potential) companies and collaborators.
- Build contest models and exam questions for candidates
- · Conduct interactive content

Achievement: Communication, Teamwork, and Academic knowledge of financial research and investment.

Duong Thanh Thuy

- Pinh Thanh District, HCM city
- ✓ duongthanhthuy8902@gmail.com
- **** 0853 785 678
- in www.linkedin.com/in/thuy-dương-2a11721bb

Career Path

Short-term goal: Aim 3.5/4.0 of GPA in University. Complete the second level of FRM. Become a student intern in investment banking, and gain experience for future career after graduating.

Long-term goal: Become a Risk Management in Monetary Risk, while learning MBA to have more opportunities for enhancing knowledge for future career.

Education

Student of Art in Business
Administration, International University
- Vietnam National University HCMC
09/2020 – 02/2024
Specialized in Corporate Finance
GPA (cummulative): 3.4/4.0

lelts 7.5

Quantitative for Financial Course, Coursera

Professional Experience

Sales Intern, SBBS

02/2022 - present

Help sales professionals maintain customer relationships by calling buyers Qualify incoming team marketing and sales Support sales team responding to basic inquiries Arrange company files

Contribute in creating support system to decrease workload and increase produtivity

Achievement: Communication, Creativity, Hardworking, and Knowledge of sales and marketing

Staff, GS25

12/2020 - 12/2021

Help customers complete purchases and locate items Train new members on POS system operation and daily activities of the store

Contribute in customer service strategies and sales goals

Achievement: Communication, Leadership, and Organisation.

Skills

Enterprise Evaluation • • • • • • Using fluently CAPM, WACC, & Gordon Growth Model

Critical Thinking • • • • • •

Communication • • • •

Hard-working • • • • •

Teamwork • • • • •

Microsoft Office (Excel), SQL ● ● ● ● Query, Python, & Power Bl